tutuapp.vip 2017-11-20

# Private Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the website www.tutuapp.com and other websites associated with such URL (collectively the "Website") powered by Shenzhen Tuxun Technology Co. Ltd("The Company"). By using the Website, you consent to the practices described herein. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect company and customer feedback. You should periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of our practices. Your continued use of the Website following any changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of those changes.

## Collection of your Personal Information

The Company may collect through some portions of the Website personal identifiable information, such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address ("Personal Information"). We may also collect anonymous demographic and usage pattern information which is not unique to you, such as your geographic area, age, gender, preferences, interests, favorites, log-in frequency, purchase history, and usage history. This demographic and usage pattern information is not considered Personal Information except when it is used in conjunction with other information that personally identifies you.

We may aggregate your demographic and/or technical information to help us understand our users' trends and needs, and to improve the quality of our services. Such aggregated data will remove personally-identifying information and will not be considered Personal Information.

Please keep in mind that any information you post on or send through the Website's discussion forums, messaging functions is publicly available and not confidential. If you disclose your Personal Information or other personally sensitive data through such channels, it may be collected and used by others, and The Company shall not be liable for any resulting claims, losses, or damages.

Please also note that when you visit third-party websites linked to or from the Website, any information you disclose on those third-party websites is subject to their privacy policies and practices. The Company shall not be responsible for the practices of any third-party websites. You should carefully review each third-party website's privacy policy.

## What other types of information may we collect?

For some activities, your web browser or client software may transmit certain geographic information or information regarding your computer (capabilities, game data processing, etc.) to The Company. The Company may use this information to generate aggregate statistics about our user community and may provide such information to advertisers and/or our partners. In addition, The Company may use such information for security, system integrity (the prevention of hacking, cheats, etc.), or enforcement purposes. From time to time, we may also post customer testimonials that contain personally identifiable information on The Company's websites. However, we will obtain the customer's consent to post these testimonials prior to publication in accordance with the applicable Terms of Services (TOS).

## Use of your Personal Information

We use your Personal Information to: (a) operate the Website and provide the services we offer; (b) deliver the services you request; (c) provide technical support; (d) verify any online payment, telephone payment, and pre-paid card transactions, which are solely processed through third-party service providers with their own privacy policies for which we are not responsible; (e) investigate alleged fraud, infringement, or other misconduct; (f) send you newsletters; and (g) inform you about other products, services, events, and promotions available from The Company or its affiliates. We may also use your Personal Information to contact you via surveys or other research regarding your opinion of any current and potential services. We may share Personal Information with our service providers who need access to such information in order to complete the work they have been engaged to do. In some cases, such service providers may directly collect Personal Information from you on our behalf. Although we require such service providers to safeguard any Personal Information received from us or collected on our behalf, we are not responsible or liable in any way for the acts or failure to act by any such service providers.

The Company's sites may also have message boards, forums, and/or chat areas, where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board, forum, or chat area, please be aware that the information is being made publicly available on-line and the user does so at his or her own risk. 

## Monitoring

We may, but are not obligated to, monitor and retain any and all data you transmit through our servers, including without limitation communications sent through or posted on the Website's discussion forums, chat rooms, and messaging functions, whether or not marked "private" by you. You acknowledge and agree that you have no expectation of privacy with respect to any such data transmitted, and you consent to any monitoring we may conduct.

## Security of your Personal Information

We use commercially reasonable efforts to secure your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Unfortunately, there are many factors beyond our control that could result in disclosure of Personal Information or any other information that you provide to us, and no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot ensure, and we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to, the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

## Updating your Personal Information

You may review, correct, update, or delete your Personal Information maintained by us. Please provide us with sufficient proof of your identity and appropriate documentation of corrections to be made. You can contact us at: [tutu.helper@gmail.com](mailto:tutu.helper@gmail.com)

We reserve the right to retain your Personal Information after account cancellation if such information is necessary to resolve any disputes or to comply with legal requirements.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy

Please feel free to contact us at: [tutu.helper@gmail.com](mailto:tutu.helper@gmail.com)
